A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18 FA290
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1; 171.6 Cubic Feet; 390 boxes, 532 microfilm reels
  - University of Kentucky (College of Medicine) - Department of Community Medicine, Extra-mural Teaching Program - Progress Reports (ME&CH), 1965-1967 (Box 179, Folder 1674)
  - University of Kentucky (College of Medicine) - Department of Community Medicine, Extra-mural Teaching Program - Progress Reports (ME&CH), 1965-1967 (Box 179, Folder 1675)
  - University of Kentucky (College of Medicine) - Department of Community Medicine, Extra-mural Teaching Program - Reprints (ME&CH), 1963-1967 (Box 179, Folder 1676)
  - University of Kentucky - Course for Health Officers, March-June, 1933 (Box 179, Folder 1677)
  - University of Kentucky - Planning for Health Center Development (ME), 1955-1956 (Box 179, Folder 1678)
  - University of Kentucky - Planning for a Health Center Development (ME), 1956-1961 (Box 180, Folder 1679)
  - University of Kentucky - Planning for a Health Center Development (ME), 1956-1961 (Box 180, Folder 1680)
  - University of Kentucky - Planning for a Health Center Development (ME), 1956-1961 (Box 180, Folder 1681)
  - University of Kentucky - Planning for a Health Center Development (ME), 1956-1961 (Box 180, Folder 1682)
  - University of Kentucky - Planning for a Health Center Development (ME), 1956-1961 (Box 180, Folder 1683)
  - University of Kentucky - Planning for a Health Center Development (ME), 1956-1961 (Box 180, Folder 1684)
  - University of Kentucky - Planning for a Health Center Development (ME), 1956-1961 (Box 180, Folder 1685)
  - University of Kentucky - Planning for a Health Center Development (ME), 1956-1961 (Box 180, Folder 1686)
  - King Edward's Hospital Fund for London - General Support, March-November, 1948 (Box 180, Folder 1687)
  - Lawrence and Memorial Associated Hospitals, New London, Connecticut - General Support, 1957-1960 (Box 180, Folder 1688)
  - League of Red Cross Societies - International Conference of Social Work, 1926-1932 (Box 180, Folder 1689)
  - League of Red Cross Societies - International Conference of Social Work, 1926-1932 (Box 180, Folder 1690)
  - Leake and Watts Orphan House - General Support, 1921-1922 (Box 180, Folder 1691)
  - Lee, Dr. Peter V. - Manuscript Preparation (Medical Schools and the Changing Times), 1959-1962 (Box 181, Folder 1692)
  - Leeds Castle Foundation - General Maintenance, 1980-1981 (Box 181, Folder 1693)
  - Legal Aid Society - General Support, February-November, 1920 (Box 181, Folder 1694)
    Formerly Voluntary Defenders Committee.
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - General Support, 1957-1966 (Box 181, Folder 1695)
  - London Child guidance Training Centre - General Support, 1951-1954 (Box 181, Folder 1696)
    See Commonwealth Fund, English Mental Hygiene Program Series, London Child Guidance Clinic and Training Center, Boxes 9-15, Folders 96-162.
  - London Federation of Boys' Clubs, Inc. - Support of Exchange Program with American Boys' Clubs, 1977-1980 (Box 181, Folder 1697)
  - University of London - Chair of American History, 1926-1968 (Box 181, Folder 1698)
  - University of London - Chair of American History, 1926-1968 (Box 181, Folder 1699)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Preventive Medicine, 1935-1941 (Box 181, Folder 1700)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Preventive Medicine, 1935-1941 (Box 181, Folder 1701)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Preventive Medicine, 1935-1941 (Box 181, Folder 1702)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Department of Preventive Medicine - Financial Data, 1937-1941 (Box 181, Folder 1703)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Histochemical Studies of the Nephron, 1946-1948 (Box 181, Folder 1704)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Histochemical Studies of the Nephron, 1949-1957 (Box 182, Folder 1705)
  - Long Island College of Medicine - Sickle Cell Anemia Study, 1947-1966 (Box 182, Folder 1706)
  - Long Island University - Development of New Educational Programs in the Allied Health Professions, 1977-1981 (Box 182, Folder 1707)
  - Long Island University - Development of New Educational Programs in the Allied Health Professions - Auxiliary Report, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 1708)
  - Long Island University - Development of New Educational Programs in the Allied Health Professions - Auxiliary Report, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 1709)
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Curriculum Planning (ME&CH), 1958-1966 (Box 182, Folder 1710)
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Curriculum Planning (ME&CH), 1958-1966 (Box 182, Folder 1711)
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Curriculum Planning (ME&CH), 1958-1966 (Box 182, Folder 1712)
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Mental Health in Pediatrics and Public Health (ME), 1948-1952 (Box 182, Folder 1713)
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Mental Health in Pediatrics and Public Health (ME), 1948-1952 (Box 182, Folder 1714)
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Mental Health in Pediatrics and Public Health (ME), 1948-1952 (Box 182, Folder 1715)
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Mental Health in Pediatrics and Public Health (ME), 1948-1952 (Box 182, Folder 1716)
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Mental Health in Pediatrics and Public Health (ME), 1953-1956 (Box 183, Folder 1717)
  - University of Louisville (School of Medicine) - Mental Health in Pediatrics and Public Health (ME), 1953-1956 (Box 183, Folder 1718)
  - Maine Medical Center - Medical Educational Program (ME&CH), 1953-1968 (Box 183, Folder 1719)
  - Maine Medical Center - Medical Educational Program (ME&CH), 1953-1968 (Box 183, Folder 1720)
  - Maine Medical Center - Medical Educational Program (ME&CH), 1953-1968 (Box 183, Folder 1721)
  - Maine Medical Center - Medical Educational Program (ME&CH), 1953-1968 (Box 183, Folder 1722)
  - Maine Medical Center - Medical Educational Program (ME&CH), 1953-1968 (Box 183, Folder 1723)
  - Marine Biological Laboratory - Support and Development of a Library, 1976-1979 (Box 183, Folder 1724)
  - University of Maryland (School of Law) - Conference on Medical Malpractice Crisis, 1975-1977 (Box 183, Folder 1725)
  - University of Maryland (School of Law) - Conference on Medical Malpractice Crisis, 1975-1977 (Box 183, Folder 1726)
  - Massachusetts Department of Mental Health - Travel to Study New Developments in Mental Hospital Patient Care Programs, 1957-1961 (Box 183, Folder 1727)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937 (Box 184, Folder 1728)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937 (Box 184, Folder 1729)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937 (Box 184, Folder 1730)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937 (Box 184, Folder 1731)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937 (Box 184, Folder 1732)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937 (Box 184, Folder 1733)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937 (Box 184, Folder 1734)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937 (Box 184, Folder 1735)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study, 1930-1937 (Box 184, Folder 1736)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study - Financial Data, 1930-1932 (Box 184, Folder 1737)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study - Financial Data, 1933-1938 (Box 185, Folder 1738)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Pneumonia Study - Financial Data, 1933-1938 (Box 185, Folder 1739)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Use of the Vaginal Smear Diagnostic Technic in the State Cancer Program, 1944-1947 (Box 185, Folder 1740)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Use of the Vaginal Smear Diagnostic Technic in the State Cancer Program, 1944-1947 (Box 185, Folder 1741)
  - Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Use of the Vaginal Smear Diagnostic Technic in the State Cancer Program - Financial Data, 1944-1947 (Box 185, Folder 1742)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Baker Memorial Study, 1937-1941 (Box 185, Folder 1743)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Baker Memorial Study, 1937-1941 (Box 185, Folder 1744)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Cellular Metabolism Studies, 1942-1947 (Box 185, Folder 1745)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Cellular Metabolism Studies, 1942-1947 (Box 185, Folder 1746)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Cellular Metabolism Studies, 1948-1956 (Box 186, Folder 1747)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Cellular Metabolism Studies - Financial Data, 1942-1952 (Box 186, Folder 1748)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Cellular Metabolism Studies - Financial Data, 1942-1952 (Box 186, Folder 1749)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Coronary Artery Disease Study, 1947-1953 (Box 186, Folder 1750)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Coronary Artery Disease Study, 1947-1953 (Box 186, Folder 1751)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Coronary Artery Disease Study, 1947-1953 (Box 186, Folder 1752)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Interprofessional Care of the Ambulatory Patient (ME&CH), 1966-1969 (Box 186, Folder 1753)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner Program, 1968-1969 (Box 186, Folder 1754)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner Program, 1969-1974 (Box 187, Folder 1755)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner Program, 1969-1974 (Box 187, Folder 1756)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner Program, 1969-1974 (Box 187, Folder 1757)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner Program, 1969-1974 (Box 187, Folder 1758)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Department of Psychology - General Support (MR), 1964-1968 (Box 187, Folder 1759)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Department of Psychology - General Support (MR), 1964-1968 (Box 187, Folder 1760)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Department of Psychology - General Support (MR), 1964-1968 (Box 187, Folder 1761)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Planning for MIT's Future Role in Medical and Health Services, January-November, 1967 (Box 187, Folder 1762)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Planning for MIT's Future Role in Medical and Health Services, 1967-1969 (Box 188, Folder 1763)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Training for Medical Research (ME), 1950-1963 (Box 188, Folder 1764)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Training for Medical Research (ME), 1950-1963 (Box 188, Folder 1765)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Training for Medical Research (ME), 1950-1963 (Box 188, Folder 1766)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Training for Medical Research (ME), 1950-1963 (Box 188, Folder 1767)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Training for Medical Research (ME), 1950-1963 (Box 188, Folder 1768)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology (ME&CH), 1968-1971 (Box 188, Folder 1769)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology (ME&CH), 1968-1971 (Box 188, Folder 1770)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology (ME&CH), 1968-1971 (Box 188, Folder 1771)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology (ME&CH), 1971-1980 (Box 189, Folder 1772)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology (ME&CH), 1971-1980 (Box 189, Folder 1773)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967-1978 (Box 189, Folder 1774)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967-1978 (Box 189, Folder 1775)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967-1978 (Box 189, Folder 1776)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967-1978 (Box 189, Folder 1777)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967-1978 (Box 189, Folder 1778)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology-Harvard University Joint Program in Health Sciences and Technology - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967-1978 (Box 189, Folder 1779)
  - Massachusetts Society for Mental Hygiene - Survey, 1929-1931 (Box 190, Folder 1780)
  - Maternity Center Association - Development of Procedures for Operating and Evaluating a Model Clinic for Maternity Care, 1975-1978 (Box 190, Folder 1781)
  - Maternity Center Association - Development of Procedures for Operating and Evaluating a Model Clinic for Maternity Care, 1975-1978 (Box 190, Folder 1782)
  - Maternity Center Association - Development of Procedures for Operating and Evaluating a Model Clinic for Maternity Care, 1975-1978 (Box 190, Folder 1783)
  - Maternity Center Association - Development of Procedures for Operating and Evaluating a Model Clinic for Maternity Care, 1975-1978 (Box 190, Folder 1784)
  - Maternity Center Association - General Support, 1920-1922 (Box 190, Folder 1785)
  - Maternity Center Association - National Program to Expand the Training and Use of Nurse-Midwives (ME&CH), 1970-1973 (Box 190, Folder 1786)
  - Maternity Center Association - National Program to Expand the Training and Use of Nurse-Midwives (ME&CH), 1970-1973 (Box 190, Folder 1787)
  - Maternity Center Association - National Program to Expand the Training and Use of Nurse-Midwives (ME&CH), 1970-1973 (Box 190, Folder 1788)
  - Maternity Center Association - National Program to Expand the Training and Use of Nurse-Midwives (ME&CH), 1970-1973 (Box 190, Folder 1789)
  - Maternity Center Association - National Program to Expand the Training and Use of Nurse-Midwives (ME&CH), 1974-1980 (Box 191, Folder 1790)
  - Maternity Center Association - National Program to Expand the Training and Use of Nurse-Midwives (ME&CH), 1974-1980 (Box 191, Folder 1791)
  - Maternity Center Association - National Program to Expand the Training and Use of Nurse-Midwives - Reprints (ME&CH), 1970-1976 (Box 191, Folder 1792)
  - Maternity Center Association - Professional Seminar Concerned with Family Health, 1967-1970 (Box 191, Folder 1793)
  - Mayo Foundation - Establishment of a Medical School within the Mayo Institution (ME&CH), 1970-1978 (Box 191, Folder 1794)
  - Mayo Foundation - Establishment of a Medical School within the Mayo Institution (ME&CH), 1970-1978 (Box 191, Folder 1795)
  - Mayo Foundation - Establishment of a Medical School within the Mayo Institution (ME&CH), 1970-1978 (Box 191, Folder 1796)
  - Mayo Foundation - Establishment of a Medical School within the Mayo Institution (ME&CH), 1970-1978 (Box 191, Folder 1797)
  - Mayo Foundation - Establishment of a Medical School within the Mayo Institution- Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1969-1970 (Box 191, Folder 1798)
  - Mayo Foundation - Establishment of a Medical School within the Mayo Institution- Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1971-1978 (Box 192, Folder 1799)
  - McGill University - Conference on Evaluation in Medicine (Internal), "Opportunities for Sharing on an International Basis," (Copenhagen), 1971-1974 (Box 192, Folder 1800)
  - McGill University - Medical Curriculum Survey, 1955-1962 (Box 192, Folder 1801)
  - McGill University - Medical Curriculum Survey, 1955-1962 (Box 192, Folder 1802)
  - McGill University - Medical Curriculum Survey, 1955-1962 (Box 192, Folder 1803)
  - Medical Care Development, Inc. - Blue Hill Memorial Hospital TV to Improve Ambulatory Care Services to Deer Isle, Maine, 1969-1974 (Box 192, Folder 1805)
  - Medical Care Plan of the City of New York - Fixed Payment Plan, 1944-1945 (Box 192, Folder 1806)
  - Medical College of Georgia - Study of New Curriculum Program, 1966-1967 (Box 192, Folder 1807)
  - McGill University - Medical Curriculum Survey, 1955-1962 (Box 192, Folder 1804)
  - Medical College of Pennsylvania - Program for Basic Redevelopment of the College (ME&CH), 1969-1970 (Box 192, Folder 1808)
    Formerly Women's Medical College of Pennsylvania.
  - Medical College of Pennsylvania - Program for Basic Redevelopment of the College (ME&CH), 1969-1970 (Box 192, Folder 1809)
  - Medical College of Pennsylvania - Program for Basic Redevelopment of the College (ME&CH), 1970-1978 (Box 193, Folder 1810)
  - Medical College of Pennsylvania - Program for Basic Redevelopment of the College (ME&CH), 1970-1978 (Box 193, Folder 1811)
  - Medical College of Pennsylvania - Program for Basic Redevelopment of the College (ME&CH), 1970-1978 (Box 193, Folder 1812)
  - Medical College of South Carolina - Vascular Studies of the Pituitary Gland (MR), 1956-1967 (Box 193, Folder 1813)
    See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, University of Illinois, Box 154, Folder 1423.
  - Medical College of South Carolina - Vascular Studies of the Pituitary Gland (MR), 1956-1967 (Box 193, Folder 1814)
  - Medical College of South Carolina - Vascular Studies of the Pituitary Gland (MR), 1956-1967 (Box 193, Folder 1815)
  - Medical College of South Carolina - Vascular Studies of the Pituitary Gland (MR), 1956-1967 (Box 193, Folder 1816)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study (MR), 1948-1953 (Box 193, Folder 1817)
    Original Grant to Harvard University Medical School-Brigham Hospital.
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study (MR), 1948-1953 (Box 193, Folder 1818)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study (MR), 1948-1953 (Box 193, Folder 1819)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study (MR), 1954-1962 (Box 194, Folder 1820)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study (MR), 1954-1962 (Box 194, Folder 1821)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study (MR), 1954-1962 (Box 194, Folder 1822)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study (MR), 1954-1962 (Box 194, Folder 1823)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study - Financial Data (MR), 1949-1952 (Box 194, Folder 1824)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Control of the Pituitary Function Study - Financial Data (MR), 1949-1952 (Box 194, Folder 1825)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Pediatric Department - General Support, 1927-1929 (Box 194, Folder 1826)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Program for an Educational Consultant (ME&CH), 1958-1965 (Box 194, Folder 1827)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Program for an Educational Consultant (ME&CH), 1958-1965 (Box 194, Folder 1828)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Program for an Educational Consultant (ME&CH), 1958-1965 (Box 194, Folder 1829)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Program for an Educational Consultant (ME&CH), 1958-1965 (Box 194, Folder 1830)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Regional Post-graduate Medical Education Program (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 195, Folder 1831)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Regional Post-graduate Medical Education Program (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 195, Folder 1832)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Regional Post-graduate Medical Education Program (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 195, Folder 1833)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Regional Post-graduate Medical Education Program (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 195, Folder 1834)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Regional Post-graduate Medical Education Program (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 195, Folder 1835)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Regional Post-graduate Medical Education Program (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 195, Folder 1836)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Regional Post-graduate Medical Education Program (ME), 1945-1955 (Box 195, Folder 1837)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Regional Post-graduate Medical Education Program - Financial Data (ME), 1945-1949 (Box 195, Folder 1838)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Regional Post-graduate Medical Education Program - Financial Data (ME), 1950-1951 (Box 196, Folder 1839)
  - Medical Foundation, Inc. (Harvard University School of Public Health) - Interprofessional Education in Law, Medicine and Related Fields, 1968-1974 (Box 196, Folder 1840)
  - Medical Library Center of New York - Purchase of a Headquarters Building (ME&CH), 1958-1965 (Box 196, Folder 1841)
  - Medical Library Center of New York - Purchase of a Headquarters Building (ME&CH), 1958-1965 (Box 196, Folder 1842)
  - Meharry Medical College - Developmental Program in the Basic Sciences (ME&CH), 1967-1976 (Box 196, Folder 1843)
  - Meharry Medical College - Developmental Program in the Basic Sciences (ME&CH), 1967-1976 (Box 196, Folder 1844)
  - Meharry Medical College - Developmental Program in the Basic Sciences (ME&CH), 1967-1976 (Box 196, Folder 1845)
  - Meharry Medical College - Developmental Program in the Basic Sciences - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967 (Box 196, Folder 1846)
  - Meharry Medical College - Developmental Program in the Basic Sciences - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967 (Box 196, Folder 1847)
  - Meharry Medical College - Developmental Program in the Basic Sciences - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967-1970 (Box 197, Folder 1848)
  - Meharry Medical College - Developmental Program in the Basic Sciences - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1967-1970 (Box 197, Folder 1849)
  - Meharry Medical College - Exploration of Psychiatric Teaching (ME&CH), 1956-1962 (Box 197, Folder 1850)
  - Meharry Medical College - Exploration of Psychiatric Teaching (ME&CH), 1956-1962 (Box 197, Folder 1851)
  - Memorial Hospital - Building Fund/Treatment of Cancer and Allied Diseases, 1922-1923 (Box 197, Folder 1852)
  - Memorial Hospital - Disturbed Chemical Function in Relation to Cancer Study (MR), 1942-1947 (Box 197, Folder 1853)
  - Memorial Hospital - Disturbed Chemical Function in Relation to Cancer Study (MR), 1942-1947 (Box 197, Folder 1854)
  - Memorial Hospital - Disturbed Chemical Function in Relation to Cancer Study/Physiology of Steroid Compounds in Health and Disease Study (MR), 1948-1949 (Box 197, Folder 1855)
  - Memorial Hospital - Disturbed Chemical Function in Relation to Cancer Study/Physiology of Steroid Compounds in Health and Disease Study (MR), 1950-1954 (Box 198, Folder 1856)
  - Memorial Hospital - Educational Program, 1945-1960 (Box 198, Folder 1857)
  - Memorial Hospital - Educational Program, 1945-1960 (Box 198, Folder 1858)
  - Memorial Hospital - Educational Program, 1945-1960 (Box 198, Folder 1859)
  - Memorial Hospital - Educational Program, 1945-1960 (Box 198, Folder 1860)
  - Memorial Hospital - Educational Program - Financial Data, 1947-1953 (Box 198, Folder 1861)
  - Memorial Hospital - Sex Hormones In Relation to Cancer of the Breast Study - Financial Data, 1939-1942 (Box 198, Folder 1862)
  - Memorial Hospital - Sex Hormones In Relation to Cancer of the Breast Study - Financial Data, 1939-1942 (Box 198, Folder 1863)
  - Memorial University of Newfoundland - Feasibility of Establishing a Health Sciences Center Study (ME&CH), 1965-1969 (Box 198, Folder 1864)
  - Memorial University of Newfoundland - Feasibility of Establishing a Health Sciences Center Study - Auxiliary Reports (ME&CH), 1966 (Box 199, Folder 1865)